Guide to the Shael Shapiro Papers MSS.200
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Architectural Records
  - Job: 7863, 208 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Job: 8537, 400 West Broadway, 1988 (Box 25)
  - Job: 7833, 366 Broadway, 1978-1980 (Box 26)
  - Job: 7867, 33 Bleecker Street, 1979-1981 (Box 27)
  - Job: 8232, 130 Prince Street, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - Job: 8224, 627 Greenwich Street, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Job: 7871 / 7901 / 8411, 64-68 Wooster Street, 1979-1986 (Box 30)
  - Job: 8316, 382 West Broadway, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Job: 7001, 21 Bond Street, William Israel's Farm Artists' Coop, 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - Job: 7004, 47 Saint Marks Place, Sobrino Residence, 1970 (Box 32)
  - Job: 7005 A / 7409, 200 Sixth Avenue, 1971-1974 (Box 32)
  - Job: 7011, 131 Prince Street, 1971-1974 (Box 32)
  - Job: 7008, 133 Wooster Street, Prince-Wooster Artists' Coop, 1970 (Box 32)
  - Job: 7009, 485 Broome Street, 1971-1973 (Box 32)
  - Job: 9530 A, 65-67 Greene Street, 1995-2000 (Box 33)
  - Job: 9126, 401 Broadway, circa 1995 - 1996 (Box 34)
  - Job: 7839, 43 West 13th Street, Dignan Loft, 1978 (Box 35)
  - Job: 7838, 114 East 36th Street, 1978-1979 (Box 35)
  - Job: 8224, 627 Greenwich Street, 1984-1986 (Box 36)
  - Job: 9206, 545 Broadway, 1992 (Box 37)
  - Job: 7847, 644 Greenwich Street, undated (Box 38)
  - Job: 7848, 128 East 65th Street, undated (Box 38)
  - Job: 7851, 439-441 Lafayette Place, 1981 (Box 38)
  - Job: 7626, 83-87 Grand Street, undated (Box 39)
  - Job: 8205, 84 Wooster Street, 1982-1997 (Box 40)
  - Job: 8228, 93-99 Greene Street, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Job: 8620, 83 Murray Street, 1986-1992 (Box 42)
  - Job: 8228, 93-99 Greene Street, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - Job: 7601, PS 1 Institute for Art & Urban Resources, 1980 (Box 44)
  - Job: 7603, 465 West Broadway, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Job: 7928, 427 Washington Street, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Job: 7628, 528-530 LaGuardia Place, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Job: 7630, 7-13 Worth Street, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Job: 7632, 423 Broome Street, 1984 (Box 46)
  - Job: 7635, 482 Broadway, 1980 (Box 46)
  - Job: 8224, 627 Greenwich Street, 1984-1987 (Box 47)
  - Job: 9713, 506 Broadway, 1997 (Box 48)
  - Job: 9234, 115-121 Wooster, 433 West Broadway, 1993-1996 (Box 49)
  - Job: 8205, 84 Wooster Street, 1987-1995 (Box 50)
  - Sweig Residence, Ho-Ho-Kus, New Jersey (Marc Sweig, Architect), 1993 (Box 51)
  - Job: 9036 B, 48 Beach Street, 1990-1994 (Box 52)
  - 110 Hudson Street, 1988-1995 (Box 52)
  - Job: 7918, 54 White Street, Teitelbaum Weiss Loft, 1979 (Box 53)
  - Job: 7916, 1200 Broadway, Stern Loft, 1979 (Box 53)
  - Job: 7919, 20-24 North Moore Street, 1979 (Box 53)
  - Job: 7909, 380 west 12th Street, 1980-1981 (Box 54)
  - Job: 8011, 55 Hudson Street, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Job: 7854: 636-67 Greenwich Street, 1978-1981 (Box 56)
  - Job: 8361, 382 West Broadway, 1983-1984 (Box 57)
  - Job: 7816, 54 Bleecker Street, 1984-1985 (Box 58)
  - Job: 7710, 105 Hudson Street, 1977-1978 (Box 59)
  - Job: 7840, 134 Grand Street, circa 1978 (Box 59)
  - Job: 7727, 14 West 17th Street, 1978-1979 (Box 60)
  - Job: 7820, 3 York Street, 1978-1979 (Box 61)
  - Job: 7722, 78 Grand Street, undated (Box 62)
  - Job: 7725, 143 West 20th Street, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Job: 7724, 1160 Park Avenue, Blumberg Bedroom, 1977 (Box 62)
  - Job: 8309, 413 West Broadway, 1986 (Box 63)
  - Job: 7866, 59 Wooster Street, 1979 (Box 64)
  - Job: 8718, 4-12 Thompson Street, 308, 312, 318, 322, West Broadway and 389 Canal Street, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Job: 7865, 361 West 36th Street, 1979-1983 (Box 66)
  - Job: 7816 / 8634, 54 Bleecker Street, 1978 (Box 67)
  - Job: 7817, 714 Broadway, circa 1978 (Box 67)
  - Job: 8016, 459 Washington Street, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Job: 8018, 627 Greenwich Street, undated (Box 68)
  - Job: 9242, 29 East 10th Street, 1981, undated (Box 69)
  - Job: 7105, 113, 117, 121 Prince Street, Tri-Prince Artists' Coop, 1971 (Box 70)
  - Job: 7114 A, 148 Greene Street, 1971 (Box 70)
  - Job: 7106, 133 Wooster Street, Prince-Wooster Artists' Coop, 1971-1975 (Box 70)
  - 86-31 Dongan Avenue, Elmhurst, NY, 1971 (Box 70)
  - Job: 7118, 919 Third Avenue, LIU Urban Design Association, 1971 (Box 70)
  - Job: 7110, 205 West 57th Street, Messing Residence, 1972 (Box 70)
  - Job: 7419, 155 Wooster Street, 1974 (Box 71)
  - Job: 7420, Smithsonian, undated (Box 71)
  - Job: 7421, 42 West 15th Street, 1974-1975 (Box 71)
  - Job: 8316, 382 West Broadway, 1984 (Box 72)
  - Job: 7714, 101 Prince Street, 1984 (Box 73)
  - Job: 7715, 120 Liberty Street, 1978 (Box 73)
  - Job: 7937, 148-156 West 23rd Street, 1978-1980 (Box 74)
  - Job: 7518, 480 Broome Street, undated (Box 75)
  - Job: 7524, 392 West Broadway, 1975 (Box 75)
  - Job: 7527, 24-26 Wooster Street, undated (Box 75)
  - Job: 7704, 143 West 20th Street, Koffsky Loft, 1977 (Box 76)
  - Job: 7707, 812 Greenwich Street, Judith Brown Loft, 1977 (Box 76)
  - Job: 7709, 142-144 Greene Street, 1977 (Box 76)
  - Job: 8511, 167 Perry Street, 1985 (Box 77)
  - Job: 7926, 491 Broadway, 1979-1987 (Box 78)
  - Job: 7612, 39 Wooster Street, undated (Box 79)
  - Job: 7641, 460 Broome Street; Job, undated (Box 79)
  - Job: 7615, 320 West 57th Street, undated (Box 79)
  - Job: 8311, 53 Mercer Street, 1972-1986 (Box 80)
  - Job: 7509, 125 Prince Street, 1975-1978 (Box 81)
  - Job: 7510, 476 Broome Street, 1975 (Box 81)
  - Job: 7512, 55 West 16th Street, undated (Box 81)
  - Job: 7119, 30-34 West 13th Street, 1972-1978 (Box 82)
  - Job: 8205, 84 Wooster Street, 1982-1989 (Box 83)
  - Job: 8719, 60 White Street, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Job: 8002, 69 Murray Street, 1980 (Box 85)
  - Job: 8003, 330 Broome Street, 1972 (Box 85)
  - Job: 8004, 74 Fifth Avenue, Rauch Loft, 1980 (Box 85)
  - Job: 8404 / 8719 / 8903, 475-477 West Broadway, 1984-1989 (Box 86)
  - Job: 8309, 413 West Broadway, 1983-1985 (Box 87)
  - Job: 8309, 413 West Broadway, 1983 (Box 88)
  - Job: 7303, 138 Sullivan Street, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Job: 7306, 345 Broadway, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Job: 7309, 451 West Broadway, 1973-1974 (Box 89)
  - Job: 7307, 16 Greene Street, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Job: 7806, 14 West 11th Street, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Job: 7807, 148 Greene Street, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Job: 7809, 29 East 22nd Street, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Job: 7840, 134-140 Grand Street, undated (Box 91)
  - Job: 7753, 429 West Broadway, undated, 1972 (Box 92)
  - Job: 8011, 55 Hudson Street, 1981 (Box 93)
  - Job: 7438, 97 Wooster Street, circa 1975 (Box 94)
  - Job: 7436, Long Island City Medical and Dental, 1975 (Box 94)
  - Job: 7762, 2061-2065 Broadway, 1977-1979 (Box 95)
  - Job: 7765, 373 West 11th Street, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Job: 7766, 71 Hudson Street, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Job: 7768, 540 LaGuardia Place, 534 West Broadway, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Job: 8511, 167 Perry Street, 1986 (Box 96)
  - Job: 8925, 482 West Broadway, 1989-1990 (Box 97)
  - Job: 7437, 440 Lafayette Street, circa 1975 (Box 97)
  - Job: 7736, 1232-1238 Broadway, 1977 (Box 98)
  - Job: 7737, 457 Broome Street, circa 1977 (Box 98)
  - Job: 7738, 424 Greenwich, 1973-1974 (Box 98)
  - Job: 7908, 74 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1980 (Box 99)
  - Job: 8813, 28 East 4th Street, 1986-1987 (Box 100)
  - 110 Hudson Street, 2006-04-24 (Box 101)
  - Job: 8224, 627 Greenwich Street, 1984-1985 (Box 102)
  - Job: 8401, 142 Wooster, 1984 (Box 103)
  - Job: 8402, 114 Wooster Street, 1984 (Box 103)
  - Job: 8321, 118 Spring Street, 1984 (Box 104)
  - Job: 9307, 118 Spring Street, 1993-1994 (Box 104)
  - Job: 8511, 167 Perry Street, 1985-1987 (Box 105)
  - Job: 7836, 165-169 Spring Street, 1985 (Box 106)
  - Job: 7935, 450 Sixth Avenue, 1980 (Box 107)